Guide to the Robert Fitzgerald Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1902-1986; Series I; 22.52; (54 boxes)
  - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE
    - Moore, John, 1956-64, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 1004)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1949 Jul (Box 27, Folder 1005)
    - Moore, Richard, 1977-79 (Box 27, Folder 1006)
    - [Morgan?], Connie, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 1007)
    - Morgan, Frederick, 1949-82, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 1008-1009)
    - Morgan, Murray, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 1010)
    - Morley, F. V. [(Frank Vigor)?], 1957 Sep 9 (Box 27, Folder 1011)
    - Morley, Hilda, 1979 May 12 (Box 27, Folder 1012)
    - Morra di Lavriano, Umberto, 1966 Aug (Box 27, Folder 1013)
    - Morrison, Ted; Morrison, Kay, 1968-83, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 1014)
    - Morse, Helen, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 1015)
    - Morse, Marston, n.y. Apr 15 (Box 27, Folder 1016)
    - Mortimer-Maddox, Mary, 1953-55 (Box 27, Folder 1017)
    - Mosaic, 1934 Dec 8 (Box 27, Folder 1018)
    - Moseley, Hallgarten, Estabrook, and Weeden, Inc., 1983-84 (Box 27, Folder 1019)
    - Mount Holyoke College, 1963-81, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 1020)
      Includes review and writings
    - [Mount Holyoke College English Class], 1964-65, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 1021)
    - Moyers, Bill, 1980 Oct 17 (Box 27, Folder 1022)
    - Mullen, William, 1968-83 (Box 27, Folder 1023)
      Includes copies of poems and application forms
    - Mumford, Lewis, 1971-83 (Box 27, Folder 1024)
    - Munro Smith Insurance, 1942-44 (Box 27, Folder 1025)
    - Murdock, Eleanor, 1965-76, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 1026)
    - Murdock, Kenneth [Ballard], 1965 (Box 27, Folder 1027)
    - Murray, G. E., 1970 Jun 25 (Box 27, Folder 1028)
    - Murray, Nobiletti and Kenny, 1965 Feb (Box 27, Folder 1029)
    - Murray, Philip, 1982-83 (Box 27, Folder 1030)
    - Murrow, Edward R., 1942 Jan 5 (Box 27, Folder 1031)
    - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, 1972, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 1032)
    - "N" General, 1939-84, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 1033)
    - Nagy, Péter, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 1034)
    - The Nation, 1936-56, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 1035)
    - National Book Committee, 1973-74, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 1036-1037)
    - National Broadcasting Company, Inc., 1939, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 1038)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1969-70 (Box 28, Folder 1039)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1970-83, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 1040)
    - National Institute of Arts and Letters (U.S.), 1957-77 (Box 28, Folder 1041-1042)
    - National Medal for Literature, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 1043)
    - National Public Radio (U.S.), 1979 May 8 (Box 28, Folder 1044)
    - National Translation Center, 1965-66 (Box 28, Folder 1045)
      Includes third party letter to NTC from Edmund Keeley and meeting minutes
    - Navajo, Sarah, 1948-51, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 1046)
    - Nazareth College, 1964-84 (Box 28, Folder 1047)
    - Nemerov, Howard, 1971 Feb 2 (Box 28, Folder 1048)
    - Neville, Robert, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 1049)
    - New Boston Review, 1982 Jun 4 (Box 28, Folder 1050)
    - New Directions, 1955-85, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 1051-1052)
      See also: Laughlin, James, Box 23, folders 833-842
    - New England Review, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 1053)
    - New England Poetry Club, 1976-77 (Box 28, Folder 1054)
    - The New Republic, 1935-78 (Box 28, Folder 1055)
      See also: Rosenblatt, Roger, Box 32, folder 1219 and Caplan, Lincoln, Box 6, folder 230
    - New School for Social Research (New York, N.Y.), 1950-79 (Box 28, Folder 1056)
    - New York Center for Visual History, 1983 Nov 21 (Box 28, Folder 1057)
    - New York (N.Y.). Dept. of Health, 1963 Jun 22 (Box 28, Folder 1058)
    - New York Public Library, 1972-76 (Box 28, Folder 1059)
    - The New York Review of Books, 1964-83 (Box 28, Folder 1060)
    - New York (State). Dept. of Taxation and Finance, 1941-45 (Box 28, Folder 1061)
    - The New York Times, 1978 Jan (Box 28, Folder 1062)
    - The New York Times Book Review, 1944-84 (Box 28, Folder 1063)
    - The New Yorker, 1956-79, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 1064)
      Includes copyright agreement and galley proofs
    - Newark State College, 1964 Feb (Box 28, Folder 1065)
    - Nims, Bonnie, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 1066)
    - Nims, John Frederick, 1954-85, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 1067-1074)
      Includes poem and enclosures
      See also: Writings of Others, Nims, John Frederick, Box 76, folder 2712
    - Nisetich, Frank J., 1974-84 (Box 29, Folder 1075-1076)
      Includes clippings, application materials, and enclosures
    - North American Review, 1969-70 (Box 29, Folder 1077)
    - Northeastern University Press, 1982-85, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 1078-1079)
      Includes copies of third party letters to NUP from William H. Pritchard and R. W. B. Lewis
    - "O" General, 1957-80, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 1080)
    - Oates, Whitney [Jennings?], 1957-65 (Box 29, Folder 1081)
    - Obear, Julia, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 1082)
    - Obear, Legare Hill Bowles, 1936 (Box 29, Folder 1083)
    - Oberlin College, 1974-75 (Box 29, Folder 1084)
    - O'Brian, Anne, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 1085)
    - O'Connor, Flannery, 1949-58, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 1086)
    - O'Connor, Regina, 1966-79 (Box 29, Folder 1087)
    - Ogle, Alfred, 1932-53, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 1088-1089)
    - O'Gorman, Ned, 1962-63 (Box 30, Folder 1090)
    - O'Grady, Desmond, 1968-80 (Box 30, Folder 1091)
    - Origo, Iris, 1966, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1092)
    - Orvell, Miles, 1970-74 (Box 30, Folder 1093)
      Includes copy of an article on Flannery O'Connor
    - Osborn, Emilie Sisson, 1968-69 (Box 30, Folder 1094)
    - Osborne, Edith Fitts, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 1095)
    - O'Shea, Howard V., 1968-73 (Box 30, Folder 1096)
    - Oxford University Press, 1964-84, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 1097)
    - "P" General, 1930-83, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 1098-1099)
    - P. F. Collier and Son Corporation, 1962-63 (Box 30, Folder 1100)
    - P. J. Kennedy and Sons, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 1101)
    - Page, Denys [Lionel?], 1960 Jan (Box 30, Folder 1102)
    - Paideuma, 1976-80 (Box 30, Folder 1103)
    - Pantheon Books, 1977 Apr 15 (Box 30, Folder 1104)
    - Papaleo, [Joseph?], 1957 (Box 30, Folder 1105)
    - Paris Review, 1983-84, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 1106)
    - Parker, Reeve, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 1107)
    - Parnassus, 1979 Nov 9 (Box 30, Folder 1108)
    - Partisan Review, 1949-84, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 1109)
    - Paulson, Barbara, 1979-84 (Box 30, Folder 1110)
    - Paulson, Suzanne Morrow, 1983 Sep 25 (Box 30, Folder 1111)
    - Pazzi, Allessandro, 1959 Aug 27 (Box 30, Folder 1112)
    - Pearson, Norman Holmes, 1940-84 (Box 30, Folder 1113)
    - The Pease Company, 1949-50 (Box 30, Folder 1114)
    - Peck, John, 1977 Sep 19 (Box 30, Folder 1115)
    - The Pembroke Magazine, 1974 Dec 11 (Box 30, Folder 1116)
    - Penguin Books, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 1117)
    - Pennsylvania State University. College of the Liberal Arts, 1980-81 (Box 30, Folder 1118)
    - Pennsylvania State University. Institute for the Arts and Humanistic Studies, 1980-81 (Box 30, Folder 1119)
    - Pennsylvania State University Press, 1981 May 21 (Box 30, Folder 1120)
    - Percival, Willa, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 1121)
    - Perkins, David, 1982 May 10 (Box 30, Folder 1122)
    - Perkins, Judith, 1979 Apr 19 (Box 30, Folder 1123)
    - Perry and McKendry, 1959-60 (Box 30, Folder 1124)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital, 1967 Nov (Box 30, Folder 1125)
    - Petropolous, John, 1978-82 (Box 30, Folder 1126)
    - Pevear, Richard, 1975-78 (Box 30, Folder 1127)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 1128)
    - Phi Beta Kappa. Massachusetts Alpha (Harvard University), 1974-77 (Box 30, Folder 1129)
    - Phillips Academy, 1973-81 (Box 30, Folder 1130)
    - Phillips Exeter Academy, 1937-77 (Box 30, Folder 1131)
    - Phillips, "Flossie", 1972-78, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 1132)
    - [Pickman], Hester, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 1133)
    - Pinsky, Robert, 1978, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 1134)
    - Pitzele, Peter, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 1135)
    - Ploughshares, 1975-79 (Box 30, Folder 1136)
    - Poems in Folio, 1957 Mar 11 (Box 30, Folder 1137)
    - Poets and Writers, Inc., 1975, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 1138)
    - Poetry, 1931-82 (Box 30, Folder 1139)
      See also: Zabel, Morton Dauwen, Box 41, folder 1637
    - Poetry Center of the 92nd St. YM-YWHA (New York, N.Y.), 1960-84, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 1140)
    - Poetry of Wales, 1973, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 1141)
    - Poetry Society of America, 1955-79, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 1142)
      See also: Keeley, Edmund, Box 22, folder 801
    - Pollinger, Laurence, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 1143)
      Includes letter from Pollinger to New Directions
    - Pollitt, Katha, 1973, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 1144)
    - Pomegranate Press, 1972-79 (Box 30, Folder 1145)
    - Pomeroy, Margaret, 1953-58, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 1146-1147)
    - Porter, Katharine Anne, 1949, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 1148)
    - Portsmouth Priory School, 1964-70 (Box 31, Folder 1149-1150)
      Includes letters from Sarah Fitzgerald
    - Portugill, Jestyn, 1978-79 (Box 31, Folder 1151)
    - Pound, Ezra, 1939-54, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 1152)
    - Powers, J. F. [(James Farl)?], 1949-76, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 1153)
    - Prairie Press, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 1154)
    - Preminger, Alex, 1965 Mar 4 (Box 31, Folder 1155)
    - [Pretiss], Sarah, 1971-72 (Box 31, Folder 1156)
    - Price, Kingsley, 1951 Jul 17 (Box 31, Folder 1157)
    - Prince, F. T. [(Frank Templeton)?], 1962-79 (Box 31, Folder 1158)
    - Princeton University, 1950-83, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 1159)
    - Princeton University. Committee for the Seminars in Literary Criticism, 1952-78, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 1160)
    - Princeton University. Council on the Humanities, 1974-81, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 1161)
      Includes letter from [Theodore Weiss?] to Mark Strand
    - Princeton University. Housing Department, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 1162)
    - Princeton University Press, 1957-84, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 1163)
    - Pritchard, William H., 1977 (Box 31, Folder 1164)
    - Prochazka, Oldrich, 1973-74 (Box 31, Folder 1165)
    - Prokosch, Frederick, 1939, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 1166)
    - Provincetown Fine Arts Work Center, 1976 Apr 3 (Box 31, Folder 1167)
    - Prudential Insurance Company of America, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 1168)
    - Prunty, Wyatt, 1981 Aug 5 (Box 31, Folder 1169)
    - Quality Paperback Book Club, 1983 Oct 7 (Box 31, Folder 1170)
    - Quinn, John J., 1968-71 (Box 31, Folder 1171)
    - "R" General, 1929-84, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 1172)
    - Rachewiltz, Boris de, 1954 Sep 14 (Box 31, Folder 1173)
    - Rachewiltz, Mary de, 1953-84 (Box 31, Folder 1174)
      Includes clipping and poem
    - Racine, Daniel L., 1970 Sep 20 (Box 31, Folder 1175)
    - Rackstraw, Richard, 1965-68 (Box 31, Folder 1176)
    - Radcliffe College, 1970-82 (Box 31, Folder 1177)
    - Radcliffe College. Mary Ingraham Bunting Institute, 1978-82 (Box 31, Folder 1178)
    - Radcliffe College. Office of the President, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 1179)
    - Radcliffe Institute, 1973-76 (Box 31, Folder 1180)
    - Rand, [Edward Kennard?], 1933 May 27 (Box 31, Folder 1181)
    - Random House (Firm), 1955-84 (Box 31, Folder 1182)
    - Ranieri, Ugguccione, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 1183)
    - Raritan, 1983 May 16 (Box 31, Folder 1184)
    - Rascoe, Judy, 1970-79 (Box 31, Folder 1185)
    - Read, Susan, 1951-60, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 1186)
    - Reed College (Portland, Or.), 1961-63 (Box 31, Folder 1187)
    - Reeves, David, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 1188)
    - Reid, Alistair, 1953-58 (Box 32, Folder 1189)
    - Reid, Richard, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 1190)
      Includes translation of Canto 72
    - Reifer, Robert E., 1966 Apr 13 (Box 32, Folder 1191)
    - Renascence, 1957 Mar 18 (Box 32, Folder 1192)
    - Repetto, Giovanni Battista, 1955-56 (Box 32, Folder 1193)
    - Reuben, William A., 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1194)
    - Rhodes Scholarship Trust, 1974-77, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 1195)
    - Rhu, Lawrence, 1973-84 (Box 32, Folder 1196)
      Includes application materials
    - Ricci, Leonardo, 1959-60 (Box 32, Folder 1197)
    - Richards, Dorothea, 1972-79 (Box 32, Folder 1198)
      Includes photographs of I. A. Richards
    - Richards, I. A. (Ivor Armstrong), 1943-71 (Box 32, Folder 1199)
    - Richardson, James, 1976-79 (Box 32, Folder 1200)
      Includes poems and application materials
    - Ricordi (Firm), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 1201)
    - Riding, Laura, 1937-77, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 1202-1203)
    - Rinehart and Company, Inc., 1955 Dec 7 (Box 32, Folder 1204)
    - Ritvo, Harriet, 1984 Aug 10 (Box 32, Folder 1205)
    - Riva, Catherine, 1956-59 (Box 32, Folder 1206)
    - Rizza Schreiner, Peggy, 1973-78, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 1207)
    - Rizzardi, Alfredo; Rizzardi, [Gabriele], 1955-64 (Box 32, Folder 1208-1209)
    - Robbins, Martin, 1976 Jul 21 (Box 32, Folder 1210)
    - Roberts, Walter, 1976 Feb 29 (Box 32, Folder 1211)
    - Robinson, James W., n.d. (Box 32, Folder 1212)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1952-83 (Box 32, Folder 1213)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1939 May 24 (Box 32, Folder 1214)
    - Roesch, Kurt; Roesch, Alberta, 1984 Nov 6 (Box 32, Folder 1215)
    - Rogers, Hoyt, 1972-76 (Box 32, Folder 1216)
    - Ropes and Gray, 1965-83 (Box 32, Folder 1217)
      Includes completed tax forms
      See also: Financial and Legal Records, Tax Documents, Boxes 89-90, folders 3108-3122
    - Rorem, Ned, 1953 Jan 28 (Box 32, Folder 1218)
      Includes printed publicity
    - Rosenblatt, Roger, 1969-78 (Box 32, Folder 1219)
      See also: The New Republic, Box 28, folder 1055
    - Rosenhaupt, Elise, 1968-76 (Box 32, Folder 1220)
    - Rosenwald, Lawrence, 1984 Feb 7 (Box 32, Folder 1221)
    - Rosslyn, Felicity, 1972-73 (Box 32, Folder 1222)
    - Rudge, Olga, 1953-54, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 1223)
    - Rudnik, Raphael, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 1224)
    - Rupp, Richard, 1981-84 (Box 32, Folder 1225)
    - Russell, Peter, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 1226)
    - Russell and Volkening, 1953-62 (Box 32, Folder 1227)
    - Rutgers University, 1969-76 (Box 32, Folder 1228)
    - Rutgers University Press, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 1229)
    - Ryan, Michael, 1975 Dec 5 (Box 32, Folder 1230)
    - "S" General, 1932-84, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1231-1233)
    - Sagan, Eli, 1975 Oct (Box 33, Folder 1234)
    - Saint Andrew's School, 1972-80, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1235)
    - Saint Anselm's Abbey, 1946 Feb 12 (Box 33, Folder 1236)
    - St. John, Clara, 1928-54, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1237-1238)
    - St. John, George Jr. (Jim); St. John, Nancy, 1931-85, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1239-1241)
      Includes photographs
    - St. John, George Sr., 1929-55 (Box 33, Folder 1242)
    - St. John, Seymour, 1956-57 (Box 33, Folder 1243)
    - St. John's College (Annapolis, M.D.), 1983-84 (Box 33, Folder 1244)
    - St. John's College (Santa Fe, N.M.), 1976 (Box 33, Folder 1245)
    - Saint Joseph College (West Hartford, Conn.), 1978 (Box 33, Folder 1246)
    - Saint Mary's College (Notre Dame, Ind.), 1957 Apr 1 (Box 33, Folder 1247)
    - Saint Michael's College (Winooski, Vt.), 1984 Oct 22 (Box 33, Folder 1248)
    - Saint-Gaudens, Homer, 1937 Dec 4 (Box 33, Folder 1249)
    - Saint-John Perse, 1960-66, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1250)
    - Salaan, Yves, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 1251)
    - Salem State College, 1977 Nov 7 (Box 33, Folder 1252)
    - Salmagundi, 1976, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1253)
      Includes copy of Guell's poem Ulysses and Circe, corrected photocopy
    - Salter, Mary Jo, 1980-84 (Box 33, Folder 1254)
    - Saltonstall, Robert, 1958 Jan 9 (Box 33, Folder 1255)
    - Sandbach, F. H., 1932, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 1256)
    - Sandberg, Carl, 1950 Jan 4 (Box 33, Folder 1257)
    - Santayana, George, 1948-49 (Box 33, Folder 1258)
    - Sarah Lawrence College, 1947-82, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1259)
    - Sassower, Carey, 1977-79, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1260)
    - Satterthwaite, Isabel, 1977-78 (Box 33, Folder 1261)
    - Saturday Club, 1977-84 (Box 33, Folder 1262)
    - Savidis, George, 1978-80, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1263)
    - Savidis, Lena, 1978 Oct 17 (Box 33, Folder 1264)
    - Schmidt, Douglas M., 1974-77, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1265)
    - Schmidt, Egan, and Murray, 1950 Sep 11 (Box 34, Folder 1266)
    - Schneider, Jorge, 1951-52 (Box 34, Folder 1267)
    - Schoeck, Richard J., 1951-52 (Box 34, Folder 1268)
    - Schorr, David, 1982, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1269)
    - Schramm, Richard, 1978 Oct (Box 34, Folder 1270)
    - Schreiber, Jan, 1974-75 (Box 34, Folder 1271)
    - Schroeder, Ralph L., 1947 Mar 16 (Box 34, Folder 1272)
    - Schwab, Arnold T., 1972 Mar 7 (Box 34, Folder 1273)
    - Scott, Winfield Townley, 1935-45 (Box 34, Folder 1274)
    - Scratton, Bride, 1933 Oct 3 (Box 34, Folder 1275)
      See also: Taylor, Alicia Cameron, Box 36, folder 1386
    - Sears, Sallie, 1952 Aug 9 (Box 34, Folder 1276)
    - Seaver, Elizabeth W., n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1277)
    - Sedgwick, Sally, 1971, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 1278)
    - Sedgwick, Theodore, 1984 Aug 31 (Box 34, Folder 1279)
    - Segal, Elizabeth Carol, 1976-79 (Box 34, Folder 1280)
    - Sellers, Therese, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 1281)
    - Seltz, Paul L., 1969-70 (Box 34, Folder 1282)
    - Seneca Review, 1981 Feb 27 (Box 34, Folder 1283)
    - Sessions, [William?], 1958, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 1284)
    - The Sewanee Review, 1972-84, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1285)
    - Sforzolini, Luigi-Giacomo Scassellati, 1968-79 (Box 34, Folder 1286)
    - Shady Hill Tenants Association, 1971-72 (Box 34, Folder 1287)
    - Shannon, John Kingsley, 1976 Jun 7 (Box 34, Folder 1288)
    - Shapiro, Karl Evalyn, 1964 May 12 (Box 34, Folder 1289)
    - Sharp, Alexander, 1965, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 1290)
    - Shaw, Robert Burns, 1969-84, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1291-1292)
      Includes poems and copies of third party correspondence
    - Sheed, F. J. (Francis Joseph), 1943 Sep 29 (Box 34, Folder 1293)
    - Sheffield, Lee R., Jr., 1970-74 (Box 34, Folder 1294)
    - Shenandoah, 1976 Oct 14 (Box 34, Folder 1295)
    - Shepardson, Nadine, 1964-65, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1296)
    - Shloss, Carol, 1973-79 (Box 34, Folder 1297)
    - Shoemaker, Albert M., 1982 (Box 34, Folder 1298)
    - Shore, Jane, 1973-77 (Box 34, Folder 1299)
    - Shoukri, Doris, 1980-81 (Box 34, Folder 1300)
    - Shrady, Cezie, 1971-74 (Box 34, Folder 1301)
    - Shrady, Maria, 1960 May 8 (Box 34, Folder 1302)
    - Sicre, Elizabeth, 1963-66 (Box 34, Folder 1303)
    - Sieburth, Richard, 1977-79 (Box 34, Folder 1304)
    - Simic, Charles, 1975 Nov 13 (Box 34, Folder 1305)
    - Simon and Schuster, Inc., 1983 Oct 28 (Box 34, Folder 1306)
    - Simpson, Eileen B., 1953-74, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1307-1308)
    - Simpson, Robert, 1977, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1309)
    - Sinclair, Julia, 1971-81 (Box 34, Folder 1310)
      Includes poems and poster
    - Slesinger, Tess, 1935 Mar 7 (Box 34, Folder 1311)
    - Sloane, T. O'Connor, 1951 Jul 3 (Box 34, Folder 1312)
    - Slocum, John J., 1978 (Box 34, Folder 1313)
    - Sly, Allan Bernard, 1936-37, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1314)
    - Smart, Allen, 1934-38, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1315)
    - Smith College, 1974-75, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1316)
    - Smith, William Jay, 1981-84 (Box 35, Folder 1317)
    - Snyder, Gary, 1975-76 (Box 35, Folder 1318)
    - Snyder, Tepper and Berlin, 1967-76 (Box 35, Folder 1319)
      Includes will dating from 1975
    - Society for the Study of Myth and Tradition, 1982 Oct 29 (Box 35, Folder 1320)
    - Solnik, Claude, 1983, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1321)
    - Solomon, Edward C., 1952-57 (Box 35, Folder 1322)
      Includes letter from Solomon to American Embassy in Rome
    - Southern Comparative Literature Association, 1977-78 (Box 35, Folder 1323)
    - Southern Illinois University Press, 1975-78 (Box 35, Folder 1324)
    - The Southern Review, 1966-74 (Box 35, Folder 1325)
    - Southwest State University, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 1326)
    - Spacks, Barry, 1976, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 1327)
    - Speaight, Bridget, 1977-83, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1328)
    - Speaight, Robert, 1957-72 (Box 35, Folder 1329)
    - Spellman, Francis, 1948 Jul 21 (Box 35, Folder 1330)
    - Spicilegio Moderno, 1975 Jun (Box 35, Folder 1331)
    - Spivack, Kathleen, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 1332)
    - Springfield Marine Bank, 1944-80 (Box 35, Folder 1333-1336)
      Includes financial statements and letter from Springfield Marine Bank to Walker and Latton
      See also: Financial and Legal Records, Tax Documents, Box 89, folders 3099-3102
    - Stagg, Brian L., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1337)
    - Stallings, W. Sidney, 1941, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1338)
    - Stamford Federal Savings and Loan Association, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 1339)
    - Stanford University. Dept. of English, 1980, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 1340)
    - Starbuck, George; Starbuck, Kathy, 1967-82 (Box 35, Folder 1341)
    - Starr, William W., 1977 Dec 21 (Box 35, Folder 1342)
    - State University of New York at Stony Brook, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 1343)
    - Steir, Vivian, 1981-84, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1344)
    - Stephenson, Gregory, 1981-82 (Box 35, Folder 1345)
    - Stern, Jill, 1971-78 (Box 35, Folder 1346)
    - Stern, Tom, 1977-78 (Box 35, Folder 1347)
    - Stewart, Zeph; Stewart, Diane, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 1348)
    - [Stockton?], Anne, 1941-46, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1349)
    - Stockton, Herbert, 1936-39, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1350)
    - Stockton, Miriam, 1932-39, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1351)
    - Stone, Dora, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 1352)
    - Stone, Forrest, 1979-84 (Box 35, Folder 1353)
    - Stone, Geoffrey, 1954-55 (Box 35, Folder 1354)
    - Stoneburner, Tony, 1977 Jul 20 (Box 35, Folder 1355)
    - Strand, Mark, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 1356)
    - Strier, Richard; Hellerstein, Kathryn, 1983-84 (Box 35, Folder 1357)
    - Stritch, Thomas, 1957-71 (Box 35, Folder 1358)
      Includes copy of letter from Stritch to Regina O'Connor
    - Strouse, Jean, 1975-79 (Box 35, Folder 1359)
      Includes third party correspondence and clipping
    - Stuart Wright, Publishers, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1360)
    - Styron, William, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 1361)
    - Sullivan, Donald Mark, 1957-68 (Box 35, Folder 1362)
    - Sullivan, Frank R., 1984 (Box 35, Folder 1363)
    - Sullivan, Richard, 1953 May 5 (Box 35, Folder 1364)
    - Sulzberger, C. L. (Cyrus Leo), 1976 Mar 1 (Box 35, Folder 1365)
    - Swan, Emma, 1937-51, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 1366-1367)
      Includes poems, drawing, and enclosures
    - Swann, Brian, 1979 Feb 18 (Box 36, Folder 1368)
    - Sweeney, Francis, 1966-73 (Box 36, Folder 1369)
    - Sweeney, James Johnson, 1951 Sep 15 (Box 36, Folder 1370)
    - Sweeney, John L., 1937-83, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 1371-1373)
    - Sweeney, Marie, 1959-71 (Box 36, Folder 1374)
    - Swett, Benjamin, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 1375)
      Includes poems and story
    - "T" General, 1932-83, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 1376)
    - TABA, 1979, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 1377)
    - The Tablet, 1966-68 (Box 36, Folder 1378)
    - Tagliabue, John, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 1379)
    - Taplinger Publishing, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 1380)
    - Tate, Alan, 1939-67, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 1381-1383)
    - Tate, J. O., 1979 Jan 21 (Box 36, Folder 1384)
    - Tate, Robert L., 1934 (Box 36, Folder 1385)
    - Taylor, A. Cameron (Alicia Cameron), n.d. (Box 36, Folder 1386)
    - Taylor, Harold, 1949-51 (Box 36, Folder 1387)
    - Taylor, Peter; Taylor, Eleanor, 1956-78, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 1388)
    - Teacher's Insurance and Annuity Association, 1951-76 (Box 36, Folder 1389)
    - Temple University Press, 1971 Jul 26 (Box 36, Folder 1390)
    - Tener, Robert L., 1975 Feb 27 (Box 36, Folder 1391)
    - Tennis Club of Perugia, 1967-73 (Box 36, Folder 1392)
    - Terrie, Henry L., 1983 Jun 8 (Box 36, Folder 1393)
    - Texaco, Inc., 1961, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 1394)
    - Theobald, John, 1978-82, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 1395)
      Includes copies of translations
    - Theroux, Alexander, 1973-77, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 1396)
    - Theroux, Peter, 1975-76 (Box 36, Folder 1397)
      Includes copies of writings
    - Thompson, Bill, 1978-79 (Box 37, Folder 1398)